# **Tejveer Randhawa**

116 Archdekin Drive, Brampton, ON

Tejveerrandhawa65@gmail.com | 647-967-6998 | https://www.linkedin.com/in/tejveerrandhawa/

# **Professional Summary**

Solution-driven Software Developer excelling in a highly collaborative work environment, finding solutions to challenges and focused on customer satisfaction. Experienced in building high-quality products for desktop, phone and mobile app users while meeting standards for technical design, user experience, usability and speed .Effective coding, testing and debugging skills in JavaScript, React, .NET, C++, C, JAVA, SQL, HTML, CSS, Swift.

### Skills

- Collaborate with Team Members to establish clear definitions, cooperation and agreements on the roles of partners in the development process.
- Meticulous and strong analytical skills with effective planning and time management capabilities
- Modifying software to fix errors, adapt it to new hardware, improve its performance, or upgrade interfaces.

## **Education**

## **Software Development and Network Engineering**

Sheridan College, Brampton, ON Sept 2016 – Dec 2019

#### Relevant Coursework in

RDBMS Application Development
Mobile Java Application Dev 2
Mobile Web-Based Application Development
Object-Oriented Program 2 Java
Advanced .NET Server

Web Services using .NET & C# Web Programming Data Network Design/Config Database Admin. & Security Enterprise Java Development

# **Project Work Experience**

#### **Battle Lands Royale**

Software Developer (Sept 2019 – Dec 2019)

- Developed a Battle Royale Game in Unity and Unreal Engines using C++ and Blueprints.
- Designed AI Bot to improve gameplay and interactive user experience.
- Successfully applied .NET Frameworks and SQL Databases to Store Player's Records.

#### **Ecommerce Website**

Web Developer (Aug 2019 – Sept 2019)

- Converted mock-ups into HTML, JavaScript, AJAX and JSON for an Ecommerce Startup Website.
- Rebuilt the home page, improving page load time by 3 seconds with updated code.
- Achieved a 20% uplift in conversion rates by implementing social login and profile autofill functionality using OAuth with JavaScript.